That today Nifty Bank declined completely,
so all the banks had declines at different times
and IDFC First Bank also had a
decline of 2.5%. So if you
want to buy IDFC First Bank,
you like the idea feedback, you feel that
in the coming time it can become Net HDFC Bank, in the
coming 10 years, 20 years, you
want to make a long term investment, then we will
discuss the bank level for you, so
if you get it around ₹50, there is
very strong support around ₹50, then you can
take a dip there and apart from this, if we
talk about Rasik, then it is fine that this is also there, if
you look here also, if we look
inside two lines, then you get deposits around ₹50, then you
can make your purchase here actively, bank deposits are
available in First Bank and if you
want to avoid it because
IDFC First Bank, brother, it is
not a multibagger bank, not a blue chip bank,
then you can look around HDFC Bank,
Gypsy Bank and Kotak Bank are quite
reasonable.  The price is coming around, so you
can see in their video
that I like it a lot, while HDFC Bank,
Kotak Bank, ICICI Bank and Axis Bank,
these are the four banks which I
like the most among private banks and the rest is
IDFC, in the coming time it may become a
blue chip or a multibagger but as of now
I do
not see anything special in it, but if you think that Twitter will
do something then you can buy No Doubt, you
cannot do it short term, on buying here it
comes up for around Rs 50, its
registration can be done here for short term as
well and if you want to keep the rest for long term then you
can keep it in lumps also, it is
your wish, it is your money, you
can ask the financial advisor, like the rest of the videos, if you are
new to the channel then
subscribe and share the rest of the videos,
Jai Hind friends